## MARILYNE BASSOULOU

+447456679366

marilynebassoulow@gmail.com

https://marilynebassoulou.artstation.com

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Recent MSc graduate in Computer Animation and Visual Effects from Bournemouth University. My background in computer science and animation, combined with hands-on experience in digital media and content creation, enables me to bridge the gap between art and technology.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Bandstand Merchandise Services** 

Part-time live event sales representative

Sales person selling merchandise at concerts and events

United Kingdom

November 2023 - Present

Lebanon

Plan A Experience Design Studio

April 2022 - July 2022 Intern

3D mapping, content creation using After Effects, Photoshop,

3D Max, and Blender

Freelancer

Freelance Tutor January 2017 - March 2022

**EDUCATION** 

**Bournemouth University** 

MSc Computer Animation & Visual Effects

Merit

United Kingdom

September 2023 – September 2024

September 2017– June 2022

**Notre Dame University-Louaize** 

Bachelors Computer Science-Computer Graphics & Animation

Cum Laude

Lebanon

March 2014- June 2017

Lebanon

# CREATIVE AND TECHNICAL SKILLS

Autodesk (3DS Max, Maya)

• Microsoft (Word, Excel, PowerPoint,Outlook)

• ZBrush

• NUKE (NUKEX)

Sagesse High School

High School Diploma

• Redshift render

Python

• Visual Studio Code (C++ / C#)

- Adobe (Photoshop, After Effects, Illustrator)
- Unity
- Houdini
- Vray render
- Linux
- Ot

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Communication

• Teamwork

• Time Management

- Problem Solving
- Attention to Detail
- Work Ethic

## LANGUAGES

• English Arabic French